# YASH PRAJAPATI

9537496805 • prajapatiyash8817@gmail.com • linkedin.com/in/prajapatiyash • github.com/yash8817

#### **SUMMARY**

As a software engineer with a focus on web development, I bring expertise in AngularJS, JavaScript, jQuery, PHP, Zend, HTML, and CSS to the table. My training experience and certification as a full-stack developer have honed my skills in both front-end and back-end development, making me a versatile asset to any project.

#### **EDUCATION**

## **B.C.A., Computer Science**

Graduating May 2023

Gujarat University, Gujarat,

8 CGPA

Somlalit Institute of Computer Application,

Relevant coursework: BCA graduate with a passion for technology and a strong foundation in computer science.

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Programming Languages: Java, Python, JavaScript, AngujarJS, JQuery, PHP, Zend

Web Development: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Django, PHP

Database Management: MySQL, SQL, query optimization and database design

Version Control: Git, SVN

Other: Algorithms and Data Structures, Linux, Debugging

## **EXPERIENCE**

# Medgenome, Banglore: Software Developer Trainee

Dec 2022 - Current

- Collaborated with experienced developers to modify and optimize existing codebase for improved functionality and performance.
- Proficiently troubleshooted and resolved software defects, ensuring top-notch application delivery. Additionally, instrumental in enhancing functionality by developing and integrating new modules.

## Kodnest, Banglore: Full-stack Developer

Jul 2022 - Dec 2023

• full stack certification program, providing industry-level training to enhance skills in Python, Java, MySQL and software testing.

### **ACADEMIC PROJECTS**

# A web application for a vehicle repair/service using PHP

May 2019 – May 2022

- A paperless appointment system that eliminates waiting in long lines by converting the appointment approach to an online one
- Technologies: PHP, MySQL, jQuery, JavaScript, Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS.

# E-commerce Website built with Django to connect buyers

Aug 2023 - Sep 2023

- Online Shopping assists an online store or company to provide its customers with an online ordering system
- My main skills gained were URL routing, authorization, creating custom filters, password hashing, session, middleware, and hosting inthe AWS lightsail.

#### **CERTIFICATION**

# Certified full-stack developer, Kodnest Technology, Banglore:

Jan 2023

### SQL(Basic), HackerRank:

Jun 2022

• It includes SQL queries, relationships, and aggregators.

#### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

## Gold badge for python and MySql on HackerRank

Sep 2023

Awarded a Gold Badge for Python and MySQL proficiency on HackerRank.